

Antreas PAPADOPOULOS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

www.inthemaking.tech

antreas.paps@yahoo.com

+44 7999 435 635

6

London, UK



aithub.com/Paps94



About Me -



I work mainly with PHP on a custom made MVC like framework for the back-end and pure HTML, CSS (SCSS,Sass) and JavaScript. I worked on API integrations for companies such as Alibaba and Amazon, where I had to meet their criteria on both volume of requests and efficiency on data storing and retrieving. Although there is not always time for it I do try to also write tests for my code and my go to framework is PHPUnit.

My current project is to learn React as my new front-end tool during my free time (my website was created using React). Afterwards, I plan to turn towards my university thesis project and continue working on that as my first fully functioning Dapp. Most of my code can be found on GitHub as a mean for potential employers to have a look at my work, as well as for people to get influenced from it.

Work Experience —



Systems Engineer | Customs Clearance Ltd | London | March 2019 - Now

- > Swiftly adapting to project needs through the use of new software and frameworks Laravel / C++ / Twilio / Braintree
- > Building our own PHP framework similar to Laravel and CakePHP
- > Developing the new platform that is eventually replacing the legacy one while creating new features and re-coding existing ones to migrate over
- > Coordinating with team members to create APIs based on our versatile clients' needs
- > Using Agile and Scrum methodologies for developing our framework and platform and side projects
- > Taking initiative on front-end UI/UX improvements as well as simplification and clean-up of back-end code to keep it up to standards
- > Use of Git and Jira to maintain clear workflow and version control
- > Update and maintenance of documentation to ease in the learning curve for future developers
- > Writting tests to automate our CI/CD

Junior Web Developer | zzDot | Athens | September 2018 - January 2019

- > Redesigning and developing the company's website
- > Providing alternatives on client suggested website templates
- > Assisting in back-end bug finding, error handling, testing
- > Learning new frameworks including Vue and React
- > Brainstorming solutions to client problems with a group of Senior Developers

Student AV Support | University of Liverpool | March 2018 - June 2018

- > Providing technical support using University systems/equipment
- > Aimed to improve the teaching experience to both the lecturers and the

Private Company IT Trainee | ComNetCom | Limassol | July 2016

- > Assisted on everyday issues regarding personal computers and servers
- > Completion of custom computer builds

Summer Staff | PricewaterHouse Coopers | Limassol | August 2015

- > Aided in the maintenance and update of client files
- > Shadowed a PwC partner in their daily routines

Military Service | Republic of Cyprus | June 2013 - July 2015

- > Two year military service as a Special Forces Commando
- > Worked in a select team to carry out drills and practice scenarios
- > Taught to be quick on my feet and think outside the box

Education -



Bachelor in Computer Science

University of Liverpool

Thesis Project, First class (84%) - Property Rental Agreements in the form of Smart Contracts on the Ethereum Mainnet:

- > Aiming to break off from the traditional rental market by replacing the middle man, and in turn provide security and transparency between landlords and tenants.
- > The Dapp, called Balloo, would:
 - act as an easy-to-use portal to connect potential tenants and landlords
 - provide a simple UI to create a tenancy agreement in the form of a smart contract, making the UX a walk in the park
 - give tenants and landlords the flexibility to work through issues that can potentially arise during said tenancy.

Skills & Frameworks -



Languages HTML Css Javascript PHP Solidity C++ C C HTML Coss HTML Laravel Nue Currently Ilearning HTML Courrently Ile

0000

Vector Design/Animation

> Adobe Illustrator | After Effects

Blockchain

> Remix | Truffle | Ganache | Metamask | Mocha

Languages -



Highly

proficient

Greek 100% English 100%

Hobbies —



- > Exploring new locations
- > Researching new techbologiestechnologies
- > Trading cryptocurrencies
- > Dancing Salsa
- > Extreme Sports Skydiving

^{***}References available upon request